

PERSONAL PROFILE

As a game designer, I love to create and ensure enjoyable experiences. My previous work experience with the game engine points me as a sort of technical/integration designer, ready to work hand to hand with the engine and the rest of the team

CONTACT

- https://davidcalvosuarezgd.github.io
- davi_magix@hotmail.com
- 692751558
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/davidcalvosuarez/

WORK EXPERIENCE

LEVEL DESIGNER

CRITICAL MISS (UNI PROJECT) | OCTOBER 2019 - MAY 2020

- Live design documentation
- Level design from concept to final implementation (white/grey box, collision and prop placement)
- Minor stats balancing, ability tree and RPG progression

https://store.steampowered.com/app/1298740/Hopebrin gers/

ART GENERALISM

YOKAICADE | JUNE 2020 - AUGUST 2021

- Low poly retro modeling and animation (unity animator)
- Unity VFX editing
- Major features and core gameplay design

https://meteorbytestudios.com/ignitedsteel/

https://store.steampowered.com/app/1550740/lgnited_ Steel_Mecha_TBT/

EDUCATION

U-TAD

INTERACTIVE PRODUCTS AND VIDEOGAME DESIGN DEGREE | SEPTEMBER 2016 - JULY 2020

- Game and level design theory and practice
- Prototyping in C# and Unreal Engine blueprints
- Producing and agile work methodologies
- Steam released project